okay, here's my beef about voting. And here's my beef about it all. We have seen enough at this
point to know that our efforts are not effective. So then when do we change our efforts, adjust them?
Because if the voting is, if the argument for voting is just more voting, if the argument is
just different candidates, how does that actually change the root of the problem, which is the
banking system? How does it actually force a shift in the root of the problem? If you're just doing
ornamental changes that can fall off, I'm trying to think about it as a tree. How do you affect the
root of the tree? Well, basically you can't even deal with that tree. You affect the root of the
tree with the soil and with what you plant around the tree. And so in my mind, I don't want to hear
people talk about running for office. I want to hear people talking about creating offices outside
of office. Like fuck that government. Why aren't we creating communal offices that we are voting on
ourselves that are running things and that are literally for the purpose of filling voids and
challenging every motherfucking thing they do. That to me is what should be happening right now.
Like we've had organizers with nonprofits for a long time that are doing work in positive ways. Yes.
I want to see people who are saying they want to run for office instead of saying, I'm going to run
for office. I want, I want them to say, I want to create an office outside the office that you all are
committed to. That's what I want to see. And I think some of y'all here in the SEAL squad,
I think y'all got it to do that. And I think that you may think it means that you need to rally a bunch
of people. And I don't think that's the case. You may need maybe 20, maybe 20. And you're creating
community alliances that have leadership amongst them. Cause you know, people have different skill
sets, right? So some people are going to be like more charismatic, more able to talk, et cetera,
but they are held to a standard. You create community alliances that look like how you feel
the government should. And you can learn this from looking at indigenous governments, from looking at
the Zapatista governments. In my opinion, that is what we should be doing. And we've seen versions of
this, right? I mean, they end up being aligned with racism like the HOA, but you know, your PTA,
et cetera, et cetera. We've seen versions of this. It's not far-fetched. The only thing far-fetched
about it is that it is actively not far-fetched, but the only thing that really may make people be
like, ooh, is that it's actively saying we're not of that. Thus, we will challenge that.
Quick little story. I would never have been on Insecure had I not gone my own route to get
meetings with agents in unscripted casting. When I was at CAA, I said, I want to do scripted shows.
Those are shows that are not like reality TV, but that are like stories and narrative. And my agents
were like, we don't think you're ready for that. Even though I'd been on scripted TV since I was 12.
And do you know, I went behind them, over them, used my contacts and got meetings with scripted,
with scripted studios, like NBC, et cetera, with their scripted casting. And they found out. And
we're like, did you do that yourself? Yes. And I forced their hand to have to care. And I forced
their hand to pay attention. We're not doing that. We're not going over their head and forcing their
hand. And we keep going, thank you, Sam Mossall, whenever they do anything like Mom Donnie.
Those are my messages for Friday. Have a good day!